LESLIE PATINO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Ambitious Full Stack Web Developer with experience in management, digital design, and event logistics. My career path has required creativity, problem-solving, personal and team development, and adaptability. I aim to leverage my knowledge and skills to develop thoughtful and intelligent web applications.

EDUCATION

University of California Berkeley Extension Full Stack Web Development, 2021-2022

EXPERIENCE

Lifestyle Director

FirstService Residential, 2020-2021

- Budgeted, planned, facilitated and marketed for community events
- Hired, trained, and supervised concierge
- Head of all digital communication

Promotional Event Specialist 2013 - 2020

- Managed teams from 3-20 people
- Worked with Google, ESPN, HP, and BMW
- Chosen out of hundreds to lead regional tours for Volkswagen and Kroger.

Assistant Spa Director LifeTime Athletic, 2018 - 2019

- Implemented marketing strategies to increase revenue
- Reached locations' highest month of revenue during my time there
- Hired, trained, and supervised front desk

CONTACT

- Las Vegas, NV
- 702-763-1712
- lesliejpatino@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/lesliejpatino/
- github.com/lesliejpatino

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React.js
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery

- Server side API's
- Node
- Express
- mySql
- Sequelize
- Handlebars

PROJECTS

Ignite

- **Summary:** This application helps couples stay connected by igniting meaningful conversation and providing each partner personalized ideas to make the other feel loved, based on a questionnaire that we created.
- Role: Create questionnaire logic via Javascript, React, UI
- **Tech Stack:** MongoDB, Express, React, Node, Bootstrap
- Live Site: https://fierce-sands-31159.herokuapp.com/

Organizarr

- **Summary:** Created with the busy student in mind. Users access a personal dashboard where they can save notes, to-do lists and create/attend study groups.
- **Role:** Project management, design, UI, model creation, client-side Javascript, Handlebars, debugging.
- **Tech Stack:** Handlebars/HTML, Bootstrap/CSS, Javascript, Express, Node, Sequelize
- Live Site: dry-badlands-77030.herokuapp.com/

Map-A-Test: Find a Covid Testing Site Near You

- **Summary:** Through a simple and straightforward UI, this application displays covid testing sites based on location.
- Role: Third party API's, form validation, UI, Javascript.
- **Tech Stack:** HTML, Javascript, jQuery, Foundation/CSS, Parsley, Google and Covid API's
- Live Site: lesliejpatino.github.io/find-covid-testing/